cpalions.org 2017-01-07

# Privacy Policy | Christ Presbyterian Academy

**Internet Privacy Policy**

Christ Presbyterian Academy (CPA) is pleased to provide information to all of its visitors about its online privacy policy. CPA uses its best efforts to protect the privacy of visitors to this website.

**  
Introduction**

The Academy's privacy policy sets out the ways CPA processes personal data. This privacy policy only relates to personal data collected by CPA via the cpalions.org website. This privacy policy does not apply to personal data provided to CPA by any other means or by means of any other website. Users should be aware that if they provide personal data to other companies, the privacy polices of those companies determine the uses for that information and CPA’s privacy policy will no longer apply.

**  
Types of Information Collected and How the Information Is Used**

CPA may gather personal information, such as first and last names, home addresses, email addresses, and credit card numbers, only when voluntarily submitted. If you make an online donation or purchase, or register for an event, personal information will be collected from you in order to process that donation or purchase, or complete your registration. If you update contact and/or student information online, personal information will be collected from you in order to process the update.

The information provided may be used to send materials that may be of interest to parents, students, prospective students, CPA alumni or CPA alumni families, and to others who visit our website and provide personal information. The information may include details regarding upcoming events, Academy news, or fund-raising campaigns. Our primary method of communication among CPA families is through email and the CPA website (cpalions.org).  If you do not wish to receive such materials, you must send an email to unsubscribe and requesting removal from the distribution list. The request must include the specific email address to be removed. 

**  
Sharing of Personal Information**

Companies may be engaged by CPA to perform a variety of functions, such as assisting with donation or payment collection, event registration and payment, admission inquiries, providing technical services for our Internet sites, etc. Such companies may have access to personal information if needed to perform certain functions. However, these companies may use such personal information only for the purpose of performing that function and may not use it for any other purpose. Other than as provided in this privacy policy, CPA does not sell, transfer or disclose personal information to third parties.

CPA reserves the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the site, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any law enforcement investigation or an investigation on a public safety matter.

**  
Access**

You are in control of all personal information you provide to us online. If at any time, you would like us to correct or delete the personal information we have about you or if you would like to change your preferences for contacts from us, you can let us know by contacting us in writing with your request.

**  
Cookies**

“Cookies” are pieces of information that an Internet site transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow a certain Internet site to remember important information that will make your use of the site more convenient. Like most Internet sites, CPA uses cookies for a variety of purposes in order to improve your online experience. For example, we track the total number of visitors to our site on an anonymous, aggregate basis. We may also employ cookies so that we remember you when you return to the site. We may associate personal information with a cookie file in that instance.

Use the options in your Internet browser if you do not wish to receive a cookie or if you wish to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Click on the “Help” section of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you disable all cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all the features of this website.

**  
Links to Other Sites**

We may offer links to sites that are not operated by CPA. If you visit one of these linked sites, you should review their privacy and other policies. We are not responsible for the policies and practices of other companies.

**  
Changes to our Privacy Policy**

Our privacy policy became effective on March 14, 2014. From time to time, it may be necessary for CPA to change its privacy policy, so we suggest that you check here periodically. Any changes will not be retroactively applied and will not alter how we handle previously collected information.

**  
How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions about the  CPA Internet Privacy Policy, please contact us electronically at cpacommunications@cpalions.org or via postal service at:

Office of Communications  
Christ Presbyterian Academy  
2323-A Old Hickory Boulevard  
Nashville, TN 37215

_Source reference available upon request._
